mysms.com 2016-07-14

# Privacy Policy | mysms

Our website uses cookies to provide you with the best experience we can. By using this website, you agree to mysms’ use of cookies. [More about cookies](http://www.mysms.com/privacy) [×](http://www.mysms.com/privacy#)

Last update: February 9, 2012

mysms takes privacy very seriously. We recognize that our customers, visitors, users want to know what information we collect and how we use it. That is why we provide this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether you want to use or continue using mysms websites, mysms applications and other mysms services ("mysms Services").

**The information mysms collects:** **Information you provide:**

When you use mysms Services you provide certain information (such as your phone number, password, email address) to mysms. You also allow access to information on your phone (contact list, SMS message inbox) when choosing to use mysms Services. Depending on the type of mysms Service, this information may be transmitted, stored and used to provide you with a better experience.

**User communications:**

When using mysms Services you may exchange private messages (including, but not limited to text, images, video, and any file) with whom you choose. Text messages are encrypted and sent via SSL, ensuring the maximum security for your data. We may maintain information associated with those messages, such as the phone number, date and time of transaction, and content of the message. None of the information that you send is ever made public, unless you explicitly opt-in for that.

**Cookies information:**

Like many websites mysms may use "cookies" when you visit or use mysms Services. A cookie is a small text file that uniquely identifies your browser. mysms uses secure cookies for the mysms applications that means the cookie is always encrypted when transmitting from client to server. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can adjust your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However the mysms Services may not work properly when cookies are disabled.

**Log file information:**

When you use mysms Services, our servers automatically collect information. Log file information may include information such as Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses, browser type, browser language, date and time, what features you use and for how long, "cookies", the type and unique number of the device you use to access the mysms Service, your mobile operator and other information regarding your use of the service.

**Links:**

We may keep track of your interaction with the links we use in texts and updates. We do this in order to improve the mysms Services.

**The use of the information collected:**

In general, we use the information we collect to operate, maintain and provide to you the mysms Services. We also try to improve and personalize your use of mysms Services based on this information. In addition, we may use your personal information to inform you about developments of the mysms Services (e.g. notifying you about major updates of the mysms service) and promotional activities carried out by mysms. We also use the information that we collect for analyzing user preferences and for reporting. This allows us to improve the mysms Services, create new features, promotions and identify technical problems.

**Third party services:**

mysms uses a variety of services hosted by third parties to help provide and improve our Services, such as Google Analytics. These services may collect information sent by your Internet browser such as "cookies" or your IP request. Google's use of this data is governed by the [Google Analytics Terms of Service](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) and [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).

**Your control over your personal information**

You may, of course, decline to submit personal information through mysms Services. However, mysms may not be able to offer certain services to you. We take reasonable measures to protect your privacy (such as verifying your number when creating an account) in order to identify your identity before granting you access to an account.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, please contact mysms via email at [help@mysms.com](mailto:help@mysms.com "Email the mysms support team").

**Information sharing and disclosure**

mysms will not share your personal information (such as your phone number) with other third-party companies except in the limited circumstances described here:

  * **Your consent:**

We may share or disclosure your information with your consent, such as when you use a third party web client to access your mysms account.

  * **Service providers:**

We work with certain trusted third parties to be able to perform our services. We may share some personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to carry out the mysms Services, and only within the obligations and protections of this privacy policy.

  * **Law and safety:**

We may release personal information if we believe that it is appropriate or necessary to comply with law, regulation or legal request, to protect the safety of any person, to address fraud, security or technical issues, to protect the rights or property, or personal safety of mysms, our users or others.

  * **Sale, merger or bankruptcy:**

If mysms is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, your information provided to us may be transferred as part of that transaction.

**Information security and protection**

mysms will take reasonable technical and organizational measures to protect the security of your personal information against loss, misuse and unlawful behavior. This includes appropriate encryption, secure storage of your information on mysms servers, and limited access to authorized employees only. However, be informed that we cannot eliminate completely all security risks associated with storage and data transmission.

**Accessing and modifying your personal information**

If you have a mysms account, you are able to access and modify your personal information provided to us anytime.

**Changes to this privacy notice**

This Privacy Policy may be revised with or without your notice from time to time. The updated version of the policy will be posted on the mysms website. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. If you do not agree to the Terms of Service [EN](http://www.mysms.com/terms) [DE](http://www.mysms.com/de/agb) or this Privacy Policy, you should not use any of the mysms services.

**Applicable law**

This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Austria.

This Privacy Policy is effective February 9, 2012. Last updated February 9, 2012.
